A Guide to the A. Linwood Holton Papers, 1968-1974
Library of Virginia
- Speeches, 1970-1974. (Box 20-26)
  - Travel reception, 15 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Report to Top Management, 16 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - National Conference of Editorial Writers, 17 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Thanksgiving Festival, 19 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Appomattox Basin Industrial Development Corporation, 20 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Dedication Ceremonies of Pier C, 29 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - St. Paul's Church Men's Association, 29 November 1972 (Box 25)
  - Fifth Planning District Commission, 1 December 1972 (Box 25)
  - Republican Governor's Conference, 6 December 1972 (Box 25)
  - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 6 December 1972 (Box 25)
  - Candidates' Appreciation Dinner, 8 December 1972 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly, 10 January 1973 (Box 25)
  - Roanoke Valley Chamber of Commerce, 11 January 1973 (Box 25)
  - Dedication of J. Sargeant Reynolds Community College, 16 January 1973 (Box 25)
  - Republican National Committee, 19 January 1973 (Box 25)
  - Keep Virginia Beautiful, Inc. Awards Luncheon, 24 January 1973 (Box 25)
  - Naval Environmental Symposium, 14 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - Association of the United States Army, 21 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - Early Childhood Education Conference, 21 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 23 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - General Assembly, 24 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - Summary of General Assembly Actions, 26 February 1973 (Box 25)
  - Subcommittee of House Governmental Operations Committee, 2 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 17 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - Southern Growth Policies Board, 17 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - President's Committee on Mental Retardation, 20 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - Southern Interstate Nuclear Board Conference, 27 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Conference on Public Transportation, 28 March 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Reverse Investment Mission to France and England, April 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Reverse Investment Mission to France and England, 2 April 1973 (Box 25)
  - LeHavre, 3 April 1973 (Box 25)
  - Amsterdam, 5 April 1973 (Box 25)
  - Dedication of Philip Morris Research Tower, 26 April 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Conference on Corrections, 27 April 1973 (Box 25)
  - Republican Professional Staff Conference, 1 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Governor's Conference on Day Care Needs, 2 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Good Government Award Dinner, Richmond First Club, 3 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia League of Social Executives, 7 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Nursing Home Association, 8 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Fifth National Seminar on Year-Round Education, 8 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Republican Governor's Association Conference, 10 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Dedication of Mountain Empire Community College, 16 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia Federation of Republican Women, 18 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Subcommittee on Housing of the House Committee on Banking and Currency, May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Farmers Home Administration, 30 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Dedication of Mary E. Switzer Building, Woodrow Wilson Rehabilitation Center, 30 May 1973 (Box 25)
  - Republican Convention Dinner, 8 June 1973 (Box 25)
  - Southern Regional Education Board, 12 June 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia National Guard Officers' Candidate School Graduation, 6 July 1973 (Box 25)
  - National Conference, American College Public Relations Association, 11 July 1973 (Box 25)
  - National Urban League Annual Conference, 23 July 1973 (Box 25)
  - Salute to Industry Dinner, 9 August 1973 (Box 25)
  - Southwest Virginia Training Center for the Mentally Retarded, 10 August 1973 (Box 25)
  - Virginia State Firemen's Association Conference, 14 August 1973 (Box 25)
  - Richmond Rotary-Kiwanis Clubs, 4 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - A.A.A. Awards Luncheon, 5 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - First Presbyterian Church, 5 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - Republican National Committee, 10 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - United Givers' Fund, 19 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - Prince Hall Masons, 19 September 1973 (Box 25)
  - Richmond Area United Givers' Fund, 2 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Governor's Travel Reception, 3 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Report to Top Management, 4 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Groundbreaking, New River Valley Plant, White Motor Corp., 5 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Fleet Intelligence Center Atlantic, Little Creek Officers' Club, 5 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Founder's Day, Mary Baldwin College, 6 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Board of Governors, Garden Club of Virginia, 10 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Virginia World Trade Conference, 11 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Governor's Conference on Reading, 11 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Washington and Lee University, Historical Landmark Designation Ceremonies, 12 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Annual Convention of Virginia P.T.A.'s, 15 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - American Institute of Planners Panel on New Federalilsm, 23 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Highway Conference, 25 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Danville-Pittsylvania Mental Health Association, 30 October 1973 (Box 26)
  - Subcommittee on Housing of the House Committees on Banking and Currency, 5 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Harvard Club of Virginia, 13 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - New York Travel Writers Reception, 14 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Report to Top Management, 15 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Radford College commencement, 20 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Memphis Rotary Club, 20 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Virginia Community College System, 30 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - Ripon Society Banquet, 30 November 1973 (Box 26)
  - General Assembly, 9 January 1974 (Box 26)
- Campaign, 1969. (Box 26-33)
  - Notes, list of newspapers, etc. (Box 26)
  - Speech, Harrisonburg, 17 July 1969 (Box 26)
  - Negatives and contact prints, 1969 (Box 26-27)
  - Chincoteague Seafood Festival, 7 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Azalea Festival, 26 April 1969 (Box 27)
  - Church of the Epiphany, 25 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Second District, March-June 1969 (Box 27)
  - Norfolk Academy, 15 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Third District, January-June 1969 (Box 27)
  - Chamber of Commerce, Richmond, 28 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Huguenot Republican Women's Club, 17 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Thomas Jefferson High School, 14 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Hampden Sydney College, 17 April 1969 (Box 27)
  - Altavista Jaycees, 7 June 1969 (Box 27)
  - Fifth District, January-May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Sixth District, March-June 1969 (Box 27)
  - Lynchburg College Young Republicans, 21 May 1969 (Box 27)
  - Welfare Rights Organization, 12 June 1969 (Box 27)
  - Seventh District, February-June 1969 (Box 28)
  - Ingleside, 9 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Photo session, Waynesboro, May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Eastern Prince William Republican Committee, 27 March 1969 (Box 28)
  - Kiwanis Club of Staunton, 19 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Ninth District, April-May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Giles County Republicans, 15 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Dickenson County Republicans, 7 June 1969 (Box 28)
  - Russell County Republicans, 24 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Scott County Republicans, 17 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Tenth District, March-May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Virginia Federation of Republican Women, 10 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Northern Virginia Center of the University of Virginia, 8 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - Foundation for Independent Junior Colleges, 2 May 1969 (Box 28)
  - State Fair of Virginia, March-April 1969 (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous engagements, March-April 1969 (Box 28)
  - Holton correspondence, March, June-July 1969 (Box 28)
  - H. D. Dawbarn correspondence, October 1969 (Box 28)
  - Transportation, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Obenshain schedules, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Dawbarn schedule, 1969 (Box 28)
  - Dawbarn appearances, 12 August-1 November 1969 (Box 29)
  - Campaign expenses, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
  - Campaign and transition miscellany, 1969-1970 (Box 29)
  - Holton campaign schedules, 3 February-28 August 1969 (Box 29)
  - Holton campaign schedules, 1 September-2 November 1969 (Box 29)
  - VIP supporters and volunteers (Box 29)
  - VIP visits (Box 29)
  - Drafts of speeches (Box 29)
  - Staige Blackford correspondence, July-October 1969 (Box 30)
  - Proposed ad copy for Holton pamphlet (Box 30)
  - Drafts of speeches (Box 30)
  - Guest books, Holton for Governor Headquarters, 30 June-3 November 1969 (Box 30)
  - Certificate of Appreciation, Lions Club of Lynchburg, 28 August 1969 (Box 30)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence, etc., 1969-1970 (Box 30)
  - Correspondence and miscellany (Box 30)
  - Correspondence and miscellany (Box 31)
  - Miscellany (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, with aged (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, minority groups (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, with politicians (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, action (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, with students (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, pollution (Box 32)
  - Holton photos, family (Box 32)
  - Dawbarn photos, formal (Box 32)
  - Dawbarn photos, family (Box 32)
  - Obenshain photos, action (Box 33)
  - Obenshain photos, formal (Box 33)
  - Obenshain photos, family (Box 33)
  - GOP Ticket photos, informal (Box 33)
  - Photos with miscellaneous state politicians (Box 33)
  - Photos of wives (Box 33)
  - Public statements by Holton, pre-inaugural (Box 33)
- Transition, 1969-1970. (Box 33-35)
  - Letters of congratulation, A-D (Box 33)
  - Letters of congratulation, E-F (Box 34)
  - Letters of congratulation, G-P (Box 34)
  - Letters of congratulation, Q-Y (Box 35)
  - Republican Party correspondence (Box 35)
  - Republican Party affairs (Box 35)
  - Office equipment and furniture (Box 35)
  - Receipts for pick-up (Box 35)
  - Rentals (Box 35)
  - Inaugural plans (Box 35)
  - Inauguration program (Box 35)
  - Governor's official photographs (Box 35)
- Campaign Tape Recordings and Videotapes. (Box 36-39)
  - Tape recording, 3 radio spots (Box 36)
  - Tape recording, 6 radio spots (Box 36)
  - Videotapes, Victory, 3 copies (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Water Pollution (Box 36)
  - Videotape, In November, 2 copies (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Short in November, 2 copies (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Five Minute Show (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Omni (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Two Party System (Box 36)
  - Videotape, Reaction (Box 36)
  - Videotape, untitled, 5 copies (Box 37)
  - Videotape, Dulany Foods (Box 37)
  - Videotapes, Nixon-Holton, 2 copies (Box 38)
  - Videotape, Dawbarn (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, 60 sec., Drugs, 2 copies (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, 30 sec., Crime (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, 60 sec., Crime (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, Drugs (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, two 30-second spots (Box 39)
  - Videotape, Obenshain, 30 sec. (Box 39)
- Tape Recordings of Governor's Speeches, etc., 1969-1973. (Box 40-44)
  - Year-end news conference, 29 December 1969 (Box 40)
  - Chesapeake Bridge-Tunnel news conference, 21 January 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 26 January 1970 (Box 40)
  - Manpower news conference, 28 January 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 6 February 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 26 February 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 1 April 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 21 April 1970 (Box 40)
  - Conservation briefing, 5 May 1970, 2 copies (Box 40)
  - News conference, 12 May 1970 (Box 40)
  - State Police Basic Training School graduation, 19 June 1970 (Box 40)
  - 50th Anniversary of Vocational Rehabilitation, June 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 2 July 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, School Situation, 17 July 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, busing, 4 August 1970 (Box 40)
  - Statement on busing, 26 August 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, Dr. Allerton, 1 September 1970 (Box 40)
  - National Educational TV, 3 September 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 24 September 1970 (Box 40)
  - Constitutional Revision Conference, 2 November 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, election results, etc., 5 November 1970 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 8 December 1970 (Box 40)
  - Year-end news conference, 22 December 1970 (Box 40)
  - Special session of the General Assembly, 6 January 1971 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 4 February 1971 (Box 40)
  - News conference, 19 February 1971 (Box 41)
  - Judiciary Conference, Williamsburg, 11 March 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 15 March 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 15 April 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 12 May 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 17 June 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 22 June 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 25 August 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 29 September 1971 (Box 41)
  - Student press conference, 5 October 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, Lewis Powell nomination, 25 October 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 27 October 1971 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 16 November 1971 (Box 41)
  - Year-end news conference, 15 December 1971 (Box 41)
  - Testimonial for Lewis Powell, 17 December 1971 (Box 41)
  - Today Show, 1971 (Box 41)
  - Message to General Assembly, 12 January 1972 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 20 January 1972 (Box 41)
  - Commemorative Session, General Assembly, Williamsburg, January 1972 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 9 February 1972 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 30 March 1972 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 11 April 1972 (Box 41)
  - News conference, 8 May 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, William Forst, 25 May 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, Hurricane Agnes, 26 June 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, Cabinet appointments, 27 June 1972, 2 tapes (Box 42)
  - News conference, retirement investments, 14 July 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, Del. Warren Davis defection, 27 July 1972, 2 tapes (Box 42)
  - News conference, budget surplus, 11 August 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, 18 September 1972 (Box 42)
  - Corrections seminar, 11 October 1972 (Box 42)
  - Announcement of Ambassador Guest's defection to G.O.P., 17 October 1972 (Box 42)
  - News conference, after national election, 9 November 1972 (Box 42)
  - Education financing report, 15 December 1972 (Box 42)
  - Year-end news conference, 20 December 1972 (Box 42)
  - Hahn Commission Ad-hoc Committee Report, January 1973 (Box 42)
  - Lincoln Day Dinner, 23 February 1973, 2 tapes (Box 42)
  - News conference, Walter Craigie resignation, 5 March 1973 (Box 42)
  - News conference, 7 March 1973 (Box 42)
  - Today Show, 19 March 1973 (Box 43)
  - News conference, James T. Lynn of H.U.D., 29 March 1973 (Box 43)
  - Dr. Fred Young, educational financing, 5 July 1973 (Box 43)
  - News conference, 20 September 1973 (Box 43)
  - News conference, 11 October 1973 (Box 43)
  - News conference, Godwin Campaign, 18 October 1973 (Box 43)
  - News conference, energy crisis, 8 November 1973 (Box 43)
  - Final news conference, December 1973 (Box 43)
  - Rubella speech, no date (Box 43)
  - Videotape, Governor Holton's inauguration, 1970 (Box 44)
  - Today Show, 11 November 1971 (Box 44)
- Photographs, etc., 1969-1973. (Box 45-52)
  - Programs for Governor's inauguration, 17 January 1970 (Box 45-46)
  - Official photographs of Governor Holton (Box 47-48)
  - Governor's appointment book, 1970 (Box 49)
  - Governor's appointment book, 1971 (Box 49)
  - Governor's appointment book, 1972 (Box 49)
  - Governor's appointment book, 1973 (Box 49)
  - Governor's appointment book, 1974 (Box 49)
  - Campaign positions on surtax and tax relief for elderly (Box 49)
  - Biographical sketch of Governor (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous work files, Staige D. Blackford, Jr. (Index) (Box 49)
  - Reprint, Republican Answer to Aimless Drifting, 8 March 1969 (Box 49)
  - Miscellaneous press clippings about Governor, 1969-1970 (Box 49)
  - Reprints of Brian Kelly article on Governor, 18 January 1970 (Box 49)
  - National Civic Review, March 1971, Governors: 1960-1970 (Box 50)
  - Sydsvenska Dagbladet Snallposten, 3 December 1973 (Box 50)
  - Newspaper clippings summing up Holton administration (Box 50)
  - Press speculation on Governor's future after 18 January 1974 (Box 50)
  - Government Executive, September 1970 (Box 50)
  - Program and menu, Republican Governors' Conference, 20 April 1971 (Box 50)
  - Negatives of Jefferson's Plans for the State Capitol (Box 50)
  - Miscellaneous photographs and negatives (Box 50)
  - Photographs, 1970-1971 (Box 50)
  - Photographs, 1970-1973 (Box 50)
  - Color photographs, no date (Box 51)
  - Personal pictures, 1970-1971 (Box 51)
  - Photographs, Governor and notables (Box 51)
  - Photographs, July-December 1972 (Box 51)
  - Photographs, January 1973 (Box 51)
  - Photographs, February-June 1973 (Box 52)
  - Silly pictures file (Box 52)
  - Photographs, 1970-1971 (Box 52)
- Mrs. Linwood Holton Personal Papers. (Box 53-71)
  - Personal Correspondence, 1970-1974
    - Ab-Ar (Box 53)
    - Alliance Francaise, Richmond Chapter (Box 53)
    - Apple Butter Week (Box 53)
    - Art Project (Box 53)
    - Ba-Bu (Box 53)
    - Ca-Cu (Box 53)
    - Child Development Services, West Virginia (Box 53)
    - Colorado River Reunion (Box 53)
    - Da-Du (Box 53)
    - Distinguished Virginians for 1973 (Box 53)
    - Ea-Ex (Box 54)
    - Fa-Fu (Box 54)
    - Future Homemakers of America (Box 54)
    - Ga-Gu (Box 54)
    - Garden Week, 1971 (Box 54)
    - General Assembly, 1973 (Box 54)
    - Gifts (sent to others) (Box 54)
    - Governor's Conference, Wives Committee, 1972-1973 (Box 54)
    - Governor's Staff (Box 54)
    - Ha-Hy (Box 55)
    - HEW Regional Advisory Committee, Region III (Box 55)
    - Virginia R. Holton (Personal) (Box 55)
    - Holton pictures (Box 55)
    - Honorary Chairman of Various Groups (Box 55)
    - Im-Iv (Box 55)
    - Invitations (Box 55)
    - Ja-Ju (Box 55)
    - Ka-Kr (Box 55)
    - Kindergarten Committee (Box 55)
    - La-Ly (Box 56)
    - Legislative Affairs (Box 56)
    - Mc (Box 56)
    - Ma-My (Box 56)
    - Mental Health Month (Box 56)
    - Menus (Box 56)
    - Multiple Sclerosis (Box 56)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association (Box 56)
    - Na-Nu (Box 56)
    - Oc-Ow (Box 56)
    - Old Dominion Symphony Council (Box 56)
    - Pa-Pu (Box 57)
    - Parties (Box 57)
    - Patch Blossom Project (Box 57)
    - Pitzer Transfer and Storage (Box 57)
    - Ra-Ru (Box 57)
    - Reading Conference (Box 57)
    - Recipes (Menus), Mrs. Holmes (Box 57)
    - Republican Women's Clubs (Box 57)
    - Requests for recipes (Box 57)
    - Richmond Symphony (Box 57)
    - Sa-Sy (Box 58)
    - Schedules (Box 58)
    - Sheltering Arms Hospital, Balder Bois (Box 58)
    - Slides (Box 58)
    - Requests for Speakers for Nutrition Forums, etc. (Box 58)
    - Specific Learning Disabilities Association of Richmond (Box 58)
    - Speeches (Box 58)
    - Ta-Tw (Box 59)
    - Teenage Nutrition Project (Box 59)
    - Thank you letters (Gifts) (Box 59)
    - Theatre Arts Committee (Box 59)
    - Tobacco Festivals (Box 59)
    - Total Action Against Poverty in Roanoke Valley (Box 59)
    - Trade Mission (Box 59)
    - U (Box 59)
    - Uterine Cancer Task Force (Box 59)
    - Va-Vi (Box 60)
    - Virginia Association for Children with Learning Disabilities (Box 60)
    - Virginia Museum (Box 60)
    - Virginia Thanksgiving Festival (Box 60)
    - Voluntary Action Center (Box 60)
    - Wa-Wy (Box 61)
    - Wellesley College (Box 61)
    - Wine List (Box 61)
    - Wolf Trap Farm (Box 61)
    - Woody's Letter from Man in Texas; Woody's Tour (Box 61)
    - The World Who's Who of Women (Box 61)
    - Ye-Zu (Box 61)
    - Change of address cards (Box 61)
    - Pending file (Box 61)
    - Monthly calendars (Box 61)
  - Accepted Appointments
    - January, 1971-1973 (Box 62)
    - February, 1971-1973 (Box 62)
    - March, 1971-1973 (Box 62)
    - April, 1971-1973 (Box 62)
    - May, 1970-1973 (Box 62)
    - June, 1970-1973 (Box 62)
    - July, 1972-1973 (Box 63)
    - August, 1971-1973 (Box 63)
    - September, 1970-1973 (Box 63)
    - October, 1970-1973 (Box 63)
    - November, 1970-1973 (Box 63)
    - December, 1971-1973 (Box 63)
  - Invitations
    - Accepted, January 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, January 1970 (Box 64)
    - Accepted, February 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, February 1970 (Box 64)
    - Accepted, March 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, March 1970 (Box 64)
    - Accepted, April 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, April 1970 (Box 64)
    - Accepted, May 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, May 1970 (Box 64)
    - Accepted, June 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, June 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, July 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, August 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, September 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, October 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, November 1970 (Box 64)
    - Declined, December 1970 (Box 64)
    - Indefinite, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Invitations extended, 1970 (Box 64)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence
    - Churches, 1970 (Box 64)
    - French trip, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Mansion tours, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Muscular Dystrophy Association, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Mansion hostess job, 1970 (Box 64)
    - Thank you letter (Gifts), 1970 (Box 64)
    - January-June 1970 (Box 64)
    - July-December 1970 (Box 65)
    - Speech on Family Food Dollar, 1 December 1970 (Box 65)
    - Governor's Conference on the Family Food Dollar, 1970 (Box 66)
    - Hi-Jinx. Campaign schedule, etc., 1969 (Box 66)
    - 1776 After-theatre party, 5 November 1970 (Box 66)
    - Christmas card file, 1969 (Box 66)
    - Easter Seal Society, 1972 (Box 66)
    - Tangier trip, 1971 (Box 66)
    - Republican Governor's Conference, 1971 (Wives). Folder 1. (Box 66)
    - Republican Governor's Conference, 1971 (Wives). Folder 2. (Box 67)
    - Governor's Conference, clippings (Box 67)
    - Governor's Conference, Williamsburg bills (Box 67)
    - Group requests for mansion tours, January-June 1972 (Box 67)
    - Scheduled mansion tours, 12 January 1971-27 May 1972 (Box 67)
    - Address book hostesses (Box 67)
    - Correspondence with civic organizations (Box 68)
    - Roy Farmer, correspondence, 1970-1971 (Box 68)
    - Mrs. Callie Hardwicke, UPF, correspondence, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Response concerning Food Dollar Conference, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Governor's Conference on the Family Food Dollar, 1971 (Box 68)
    - Family Food Dollar correspondence, 1971 (Box 69)
    - Train the Trainer (Box 69)
    - District meetings (Box 69)
    - Preliminary planning of conference (Box 69)
    - Master list of invitations to conference (Box 69)
    - Summary and recommendations (Box 69)
    - Planning of Family Food Dollar Conference (Box 69)
    - Scrapbook, Family Food Dollar Conference (Box 69)
  - Distinguished Virginians Dinner 1972
    - Architects (Box 70)
    - Artists (Box 70)
    - Athletes (Box 70)
    - Education (Box 70)
    - Historians (Box 70)
    - Military (Box 70)
    - Scientists (Box 70)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 70)
    - Virginius Dabney (Miscellaneous) (Box 70)
    - Guest lists and suggestions (Box 70)
    - Invitations and correspondence (Box 70)
    - Final guest list (Box 70)
    - Wrap-up (Box 71)
    - Photographs (Box 71)
    - Photographs of Governor Holton (Box 71)
- Films. (Box 3-4)
  - The Holton Years, 29 minutes, color, 1974 (Box 3)
    Film looks at Holton's term in office, the programs he initiated or improved and the results he obtained.
  - [Highlights of the Inauguration Weekend], 7 minutes, color, magnetic sound (Box 3)
  - [Highlights of the Inauguration Weekend], 7 minutes, color, DVD - transferred from original 16mm film (Box 3)
  - [Interview with Mrs. Holton], 25 minutes, color, magnetic sound (Box 3)
  - The Holton Years: Winds of Change (2 reels) (Box 4)